<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Xavier Botar Atenista</title>
    <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Xavier Botar Atenista</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ph</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:05:14 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Political Party Registration Guide Released</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/political-party-registration-guide-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:05:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/political-party-registration-guide-released/</guid>
      <description>The XU CSG Electoral Commission has issued a simplified guide for registering political parties for the forthcoming Botar Atenista 2024. Differing the official resolution (RESOLUTION 6 - 2324), this guide has been made available at Facebook (which can be accessed via this link). The post contents comprise the images found below.
Parties have been encouraged to commence their registration starting from December 16, 2023, with the deadline set on January 19, 2024 - precisely 6:00 PM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultation With Sir Rangie</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-with-sir-rangie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:10:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-with-sir-rangie/</guid>
      <description>On November 29, 2023, the Electoral Commission held a consultation meeting with the former ELECOM Chief Commissioner and current University Registrar, Mr. Jun Rangie Obispo, in the Lolo Kiko Collaboration Space (STC 215). The meeting discussed the Commission’s plans for the Botar Atenista. Concerns pertaining to discrepancies observed within year levels in eLearn during the election period were also addressed. Valuable insights were shared to resolve these issues, emphasizing the importance of proactive measures to ensure integrity and transparency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning Phase Initiated</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/planning-phase-initiated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:03:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/planning-phase-initiated/</guid>
      <description>In collaboration with the Xavier Debate Circle, the Electoral Commission held a pivotal meeting last November 25, 2023 to initiate the planning phase for the upcoming debates that are to take place during the upcoming Botar Atenista. This gathering marks the commencement of intellectually stimulating debates among the aspiring candidates for each organizations. Anticipation builds as we lay the foundation for an energetic discussion at this term&amp;rsquo;s Botar Atenista.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultation for Botar Modules</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-for-botar-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:17:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-for-botar-modules/</guid>
      <description>On the day November 22, 2023, in the Loyola Conference Room, the Electoral Commission conducted its first consultation in preparation for the upcoming Botar Modules and Botar Atenista 2024. The meeting was presided by the Botar Modules Project Head, Mr. Adriane Lyle Ricaza and this year&amp;rsquo;s Botar Atenista&amp;rsquo;s project head, Ms. Chelsea Absin. In attendance with the said consultation was the OSA Director, Mr. Ivanell Subrabas, SACDEV Head - Mr. Andre Robert Daba and the Electoral Commission&amp;rsquo;s Chief of Commission, Ms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
