<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xavier Botar Atenista</title>
    <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xavier Botar Atenista</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ph</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elecom Revises Election Calendar</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/revised-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/revised-calendar/</guid>
      <description>The buzz is on as we kick off the election season. The Commission is pleased to officially declare the Revised Calendar of the election season! This is the timeline of activities for Botar Atenista 2024 based on RESOLUTION 10-2324. Stay informed, engaged, and inspired as we celebrate the values that define our academic community!&#xA;RESOLUTION 10-2324 Link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th General Meeting</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/4th-general-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 17:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/4th-general-meeting/</guid>
      <description>In welcoming the start of a new semester, staff members and deputy commissioners of the Electoral Commission gathered together as the fourth General Meeting was conducted yesterday, January 20, 2024.&#xA;The meeting was headed by the Chief Commissioner, encouraging communication and collaboration within the commission, reflecting achievements, and discussing important preparations for Botar Atenista.&#xA;The meeting wrapped up with a sense of camaraderie and dedication to transparency and accountability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commission Holds Second Strategic Meeting</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/second-strat-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 19:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/second-strat-meeting/</guid>
      <description>On January 17, 2024, XU-CSG Electoral Commission commemorated their 2nd Strategic Meeting for Botar Atenista 2024. In a collaborative conference with OSA director - Sir Ivan Subrabas - and SACDEV head - Sir Andre Daba - the Electoral Commission successfully deliberated discussions that highlighted precise plans and strategies for the imminent commencement of the Botar Atenista 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botar Atenista Begins - Calendar of Events</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/botar-commencement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/botar-commencement/</guid>
      <description>The commission has issued the official schedule of activities for this year&amp;rsquo;s Botar Atenista. The following are publication materials based on the official memorandum (official memorandum can be accessed here):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide for Filing of Certificate of Candidacy</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/filing-coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 18:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/filing-coc/</guid>
      <description>The XU CSG Electoral Commission has released a guide for candidacy filing for this year&amp;rsquo;s Botar Atenista. The following pubmats have been made for simplification which contains all of the required documents and activities for an aspiring candidate. Interested to be an Atenean Student Leader? File now!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commision&#39;s 3rd Plenary Session</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/meeting-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:10:46 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/meeting-today/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this afternoon, January 8, 2024, the XU CSG Electoral Commission commemorated a Successful Third Plenary Session.&#xA;The attendees finished the inaugural Plenary Session fostering collaboration and collective dedication to the goals outlined. Persevering the spirit of cooperation on this year&amp;rsquo;s planned projects, commission structure, and initiatives to promote improvement in the commission. The chief of commission, along with her associate, deputy secretaries, secretariats, and logistics, came together with a shared focus on knowledge to establish the foundation for the commission&amp;rsquo;s journey this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elecom Now Hiring Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/volunteers-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 19:10:46 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/volunteers-needed/</guid>
      <description>Ateneans, are you looking for an opportunity to become an essential part of a successful election? Good news! The Electoral Commission is now accepting applications for volunteers interested in becoming staff members. Read more of this post for the details.&#xA;Creatives are deployed by the commission&amp;rsquo;s committee on promotions and communications, responsible for producing published materials mostly for Botar Atenista 2024.&#xA;On the other hand, logistics are deployed in the logistics management committee of the commission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political Party Registration Guide Released</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/political-party-registration-guide-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 19:05:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/political-party-registration-guide-released/</guid>
      <description>The XU CSG Electoral Commission has issued a simplified guide for registering political parties for the forthcoming Botar Atenista 2024. Differing the official resolution (RESOLUTION 6 - 2324), this guide has been made available at Facebook (which can be accessed via this link). The post contents comprise the images found below.&#xA;Parties have been encouraged to commence their registration starting from December 16, 2023, with the deadline set on January 19, 2024 - precisely 6:00 PM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultation With Sir Rangie</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-with-sir-rangie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:10:46 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-with-sir-rangie/</guid>
      <description>On November 29, 2023, the Electoral Commission held a consultation meeting with the former ELECOM Chief Commissioner and current University Registrar, Mr. Jun Rangie Obispo, in the Lolo Kiko Collaboration Space (STC 215). The meeting discussed the Commission’s plans for the Botar Atenista. Concerns pertaining to discrepancies observed within year levels in eLearn during the election period were also addressed. Valuable insights were shared to resolve these issues, emphasizing the importance of proactive measures to ensure integrity and transparency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning Phase Initiated</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/planning-phase-initiated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 19:03:58 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/planning-phase-initiated/</guid>
      <description>In collaboration with the Xavier Debate Circle, the Electoral Commission held a pivotal meeting last November 25, 2023 to initiate the planning phase for the upcoming debates that are to take place during the upcoming Botar Atenista. This gathering marks the commencement of intellectually stimulating debates among the aspiring candidates for each organizations. Anticipation builds as we lay the foundation for an energetic discussion at this term&amp;rsquo;s Botar Atenista.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultation for Botar Modules</title>
      <link>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-for-botar-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:17:48 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://xucsg-elecom.netlify.com/posts/consultation-for-botar-modules/</guid>
      <description>On the day November 22, 2023, in the Loyola Conference Room, the Electoral Commission conducted its first consultation in preparation for the upcoming Botar Modules and Botar Atenista 2024. The meeting was presided by the Botar Modules Project Head, Mr. Adriane Lyle Ricaza and this year&amp;rsquo;s Botar Atenista&amp;rsquo;s project head, Ms. Chelsea Absin. In attendance with the said consultation was the OSA Director, Mr. Ivanell Subrabas, SACDEV Head - Mr. Andre Robert Daba and the Electoral Commission&amp;rsquo;s Chief of Commission, Ms.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
